Hannah Scharman

5009 W 5320 S Salt Lake City, UT 84118 (801) 556-8605 scharman.hannah@gmail.com

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

EXPERIENCE

Auric Energy, West Valley City — Customer Relations

JANUARY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

- Coordinated site visits to address technical solar system issues
- Collaborated with the Customer Service team to provide an excellent experience to customers and improve internal systems
- Maintained customer happiness with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs, answering questions and resolving concerns
- Described Auric Energy's solar systems and components to customers, thoroughly explaining details and care of merchandise

Solaroo Energy, South Jordan — Office Manager

AUGUST 2015 - JANUARY 2019

- Increased team productivity by reorganizing office supplies and protocols
- Liaised with customers and addressed inquiries, site visit requests, and product concerns
- Oversaw office inventory activities, including ordering and requisitions, stocking and shipment receiving
- Improved customer satisfaction scores through application of superior conflict resolution and problem-solving skills
- Promoted worksite and driver safety by implementing safety procedures and coordinating safety training meetings

EDUCATION

University of Utah Coding Bootcamp — Certificate of Web Dev

AUGUST 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

Itineris Early College High School — *Associate of Science*AUGUST 2010 - MAY 2012

SKILLS

Customer relationships

Customer Relationship Management Software (CRM)

Leadership and teamwork

Web development projects

Basic programming skills in CSS, HTML, and Javascript